(Penny:)What is that about?
(Leonard:)He's smart and crazy enough.
He may have actually created a monster.
(Sheldon:)Shoo, shoo.
(Sheldon:)Be gone.
(Leonard:)What the hell is going on?
(Sheldon:)There's a bird outside the window
and he won't go away.
(Sheldon:)That is the hell that is going on.
(Sheldon:)We have no worms or seeds here.
Shoo, shoo.
(Penny:)Really? On top of everything else,
you're afraid of birds?
(Sheldon:)It's called ornithophobia, and someday it
will be recognized as a true disability...
(Sheldon:)...and the landlord will be required by
Iaw to put a giant net over the building.
(Sheldon:)Which is unfortunate,
because I have a fear of nets.
(Penny:)So movies, yes or no?
- Oh, movies, yes.
Mm.
(Penny:)Great. I'll see you later.
And remember, he's more afraid of you...
(Penny:)- ...than you are of him.
- That doesn't help.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Penny:)I was talking to the bird.
Go away, bird. Go away, bird.
Go away, bird.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, just ignore him.
(Sheldon:)Good idea.
Attention is what birds want.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Much better. All right.
(Sheldon:)Now I'll just get along with my life.
(Sheldon:)Make a pot of tea, Leonard,
it's gonna be a long night.